Amanda Sealshow. Richmond City Council voted 5 to 1, so I like that it's a strong vote,
to divest all city funds from stocks or mutual funds linked to companies with ties to Israel.
So the decision was spurred by the student movements. I know Tiffany Haddish said that
they're pointless because someone told her to say that and she said no problem. So I know that she
said that, but that's simply just untrue. I just have to take a moment to acknowledge how idiotic
that is. And she's not the first to say it, so I'm not even trying to pin it just on her. She's
actually parroting things that have been said. But like, are we just going to ignore that the
student movements are what started the civil rights movement? Like, are we just ignoring that? Ah,
like student movements are what really spurred the divestment from South Africa. It's money that
allows for these apartheid regimes to exist and to persist. Anywho, let me get back focused. So
Richmond has around 600 million to invest, but only a small part of it, about 7%, is invested in
companies that the city will stop supporting. These companies include those that make weapons
and technologies. So, you know, like Microsoft and Airbnb. This is also important because then
you're going to start seeing, as this dovetails, companies like Microsoft, Boeing, Google, et cetera,
like their stock will drop. Black people, we should care because the prime example of why voting
on the state and local level matters. You have it.